adcourier.com 2014-11-17

# Privacy Policy - broadbean.com - UK

### Personal Information

You may choose to provide personal information (such as your name, address, telephone number and email address) on this website. Here are some of the ways you may provide the information and the types of information you may submit. We also tell you how we may use the information.

### Contact Us

If you contact us through the Contact Us form on this site, we ask you for information such as your name and email address so we can respond to your questions and comments. You may choose to provide additional information as well.

### Free Trial Application

If you apply for a "Free Trial" on this site, we ask you for information such as your name and email address in addition to the information we require to assess your needs.

### Questionnaires & Surveys

We occasionally may ask visitors to our website to complete online surveys and opinion polls about their activities, attitudes and interests. These surveys help us serve you better and improve the usefulness of our site. In conducting these surveys we may ask you for your name and email address. We do not keep any personal information about you in connection with your participation in a broadbean.com survey unless you specifically agree to provide that information.

### Newsletter Signup

If you subscribe to our newsletter on this site, we ask you to provide us with your email address. You may choose to provide additional information as well.

### Non-Personal Information

We collect certain aggregate and non-personal information when you visit this website. Aggregate and non-personal information does not relate to a single identifiable visitor. It tells us such things as how many users visited our site and the pages accessed. By collecting this information, we learn how to best tailor our website to our visitors. We collect this information either through "cookie" technology or with "web beacons", as explained below.

### Cookies & Similar Technology

The Site also uses cookies to collect information about your access to the Site and the services we provide and, although they do identify a user's computer, they do not, of themselves, personally identify users.

Cookies are pieces of information that include a unique reference code that a website transfers to your device to store and sometimes track information about you. A number of cookies we use will last only for the duration of your web session and expire when you close your browser. Other cookies are used to remember you when you return to the Site and last for longer.

We use cookies for the following reasons:

#### a) Necessary Session Management

Managing your login session so you can move easily from one page to another within the Site and your page requests are loaded in a smooth and secure manner;

#### b) Performance

Collect statistical information about how you use the Site so that we can improve the Site;

remembering that you have used the Site before; this means we can identify the number of unique visitors we receive to different parts of the Site and help optimise performance on the most visited areas;

#### c) Functionality

Storing your preferences and selections;

customising elements of the layout and/or content of the pages of the Site for you;

#### d) Interest-based Advertising

Gathering information about the pages through our advertising partners, on the website that you visit, and also other information about other websites that you visit, so as to place you in a "market segment". This information is collected by reference to the IP address that you are using and so does not identify you personally, but does include information about the country and city you are in, together with the name of your internet service provider. This information is then used to place interest-based adverts on the website which it is believed will be relevant to your market segment. For more information about this type of interest based advertising, and about how to turn this feature off please visit [www.youronlinechoices.co.uk](http://www.youronlinechoices.co.uk/) or follow the link to the website of our advertising partners shown in the detailed cookie list below. Without these cookies, advertisements you encounter will be less relevant to you and to your interests.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that or to notify you each time a cookie is set. You can also learn more about cookies by visiting [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) which includes additional useful information on cookies and how to block cookies using different types of browser. Please note however, that by blocking or deleting cookies used on the Site you may not be able to take full advantage of the Site if you do so.

You can access more detail about specific cookies issued through our Website or the Broadbean application and how to restrict or block certain cookies by reviewing the detailed cookie list below.

In addition to cookies we use the following similar technologies in respect of your use of the Site:

Pixel Gifs/web beacons - these are small image files that may be placed by us or third parties in respect of your use of the Site within the body of our newsletters so we or third parties can understand which parts of the Site are visited or whether particular content is of interest.

Flash cookies - Broadbean does not serve Flash cookies but Adobe Flash Player may be used by third parties serving advertisements to the Site in cases where these advertisments are served with flash related content. It is not possible to block or restrict flash cookies using your browser settings, however information on how to do this is available from the Adobe website at: <http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security>.

### Detailed Cookie List

#### a) Our Cookies

**Cookie Name** | **Purpose** | **More Information**  
---|---|---  
BEANSID | Used to log you in to our application. | Persistent   
Duration 12 hours  
USERNAME | Old login cookie used for backward compatibility when logging in to our application. | Persistent   
Duration 12 months  
PASSWORD | Old login cookie used for backward compatibility when logging in to our application. | Persistent   
Duration 12 months  
ADC | Holds an encrypted password of your login to our application. | Persistent   
Duration 12 months  
Lang | To tailor the language display of our main website. | Persistent   
Duration 12 months  
Country | To tailor the language display of our main website. | Persistent   
Duration 12 months  
  
#### b) Third Party Cookies

Cookies are also set by third parties on the Site or these are set by us using the third parties cookie code. More information about cookies placed by third parties and how to restrict or block their cookies can be accessed by following the link to their website.

**Cookie name** | **Purpose** | **More Information**  
---|---|---  
Pardot: Visitorld | Used to track your activity on our website so that we can offer more relevant content and services. | Persistent  
Duration 10 years  
<http://www.pardot.com/company/legal/privacy-policy.html>  
Google Analytics: _utma and _utmz | Google Analytics is a web analytics service which uses cookies to evaluate your use of this website. Google Analytics sets or updates cookies only to collect data required for this reporting. Google Analytics cookies do not collect personal data about your activity. These cookies are used to determine your visit sessions, identify anonymised unique visitors, identify the source of visits and navigation paths and set custom variables depending on actions taken on the site. | Persistent  
Duration 2 years 6 months  
<http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>  
[Further information about cookies from Google and Cookie time frames](http://code.google.com/apis/analytics/docs/concepts/gaConceptsCookies.html)  
  
### Web Beacons

Certain pages on our site contain "web beacons" (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons allow third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party. We use log files to store the data that is collected through web beacons. Broadbean also uses third party web beacons to help manage online advertising. These web beacons are provided by our ad management partner Google Analytics. These files enable Google Analytics to recognize a unique cookie on your web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie on your web browser was placed by Broadbean, or by another advertiser who works with Google Analytics. With both cookies and web beacon technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. For more information about Google Analytics, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to [www.google-analytics.com](http://www.google.com/analytics/).

### Information We Share

We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information about our website visitors, except as described here. We may share information provided by our visitors to broadbean.com with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. These service providers are contractually restricted from using or disclosing the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided through this website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement.

### Information We Transfer

We may transfer the personal information we collect on this site to other countries where we do business, but we will do so only for the purposes described above. When we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described here unless otherwise required by applicable laws.

### Links To Other Sites

We provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These sites may have their own privacy statements in place, which we recommend you review if you visit any linked websites. We are not responsible for the content of linked sites or any use of the sites.

### How We Protect Personal Information

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration or destruction of the personal information you provide on this web site.

### How To Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Statement, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by:

  * Visiting our Contact Form
  * Calling us at +44 (0)20 7536 1661
  * Writing to us at:

Broadbean Technology  
40 Marsh Wall,  
London,  
E14 9TP

**Please Note:** This Privacy Statement may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our online information practices.
